globalhotelindex.com 2010-12-23

# Untitled Document 1

## Applicability 

By accessing and using this site, your use indicates your agreement with the terms of this Policy. **If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use this site.**

This Policy is applicable to this and certain other Global Hotelindex web/mobile sites, but not necessarily, for which special terms and conditions may apply as indicated. All Global Hotelindex sites to which this Policy is applicable are collectively referred to as this " **site** ". Note that special use terms, or site or page specific terms (referred to as " **special terms** "), may apply to certain pages/services on this site, but the applicability of any such special terms will be expressly indicated. In the event of any inconsistency between any special terms and this Policy, the applicable special terms will prevail over the terms of this Policy.

## Anonymous Use 

In general, most of this site's pages are provided for informational purposes and you will be able to use this site without telling Global Hotelindex who you are or providing Global Hotelindex with any personal data about yourself. There are times, however, when in connection with your use of this site Global Hotelindex may need information about you.

## Personal Data Provided by You 

To respond to your questions, fulfil your requests or manage interactive customer programs, it may be necessary to ask for or obtain personal data. If you provide us with any personal data, we may use it to respond to your requests, customize your user experience with us, determine your satisfaction with Global Hotelindex products and/or services or contact you via mail, e-mail, mobile message or phone, or, in accordance with local law, contact you via the aforementioned channels to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. **By providing information to Global Hotelindex through this site, you acknowledge and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifying information of the type and for the limited purposes described in this Policy.**

You expressly accept and give your consent that your personal data obtained in connection with your use of this site may be transferred, if permitted by applicable local legislation, across international borders to server locations supporting this site (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your location) for operating and developing this site and Global Hotelindex services, including transfers to Global Hotelindex subcontractors or agents, as mentioned below, who perform tasks related to this site, or Global Hotelindex services, or for the purposes of storing the data in relevant databases, which may be located in Finland or in any other country where Global Hotelindex has operations.  
If you place an order for a product, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfil your order and/or request. Unless compelled by applicable law or administrative or judicial order, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, fulfil your requests, manage interactive customer programs or, if you are a corporate user, enable administration of access and usage of this site by authorized personnel in your organization. If allowed by applicable local legislation, Global Hotelindex may also exchange information between Global Hotelindex's affiliated (related) companies for the purposes mentioned in this Policy.

**Because Global Hotelindex is committed to protecting your privacy, Global Hotelindex does not engage in the practice of selling or trading personal data to other companies for promotional purposes.**

## Usage of Subcontractors 

We may use subcontractors to provide some products or services to you. We also may need to share your personal data with these subcontractors so that they can provide services to us. Our subcontractors are not permitted to use such personal data for any other purposes and we impose confidentiality requirements on their services.

## Visitor Identification - Usage of "Cookies" 

From time to time, information may be placed on your computer to improve this site and Global Hotelindex's services for you. This information is commonly referred to as a "cookie", which many web sites use. Cookies are pieces of data stored on your computer's hard drive or browser, and not on this site. They typically enable collection of certain information about your computer, including your internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, your browser type and the address of any referring sites. The use of cookies provides benefits to you, such as eliminating the need for you to enter your password frequently during a session, or, where applicable, re-enter items you place in a shopping cart from visit to visit if you do not finish a transaction on an earlier visit. By showing how and when our visitors use this site or other Global Hotelindex sites, the use of cookies allows Global Hotelindex to continue to improve the sites. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits. Please understand that if cookies are turned off, you may not be able to view certain parts of this site that may enhance your visit. Some of our business partners whose content is linked to or from this site may also use cookies. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. This site also makes use of cookies for website traffic analysis and anonymous demographic profiling. 

## Security 

Global Hotelindex has endeavored to take commercially reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to and improper use of your personal data submitted to Global Hotelindex via your use of this site. For example, Global Hotelindex uses encryption technology when collecting financial personal data such as credit card information. If this site supports on-line transactions, it will use an industry standard security measure, such as the one available through "Secure Sockets Layer" (" **SSL"), to protect the confidentiality and security of online transactions. If used, industry standard security measures like SSL authentication ensure that credit card information, as well as other personal data submitted as part of the buying process, is reasonably safe from third party interception.**

there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or via the internet or other technologies, and no system of technology is completely safe or "tamper"/"hacker" proof, Global Hotelindex has endeavored to take reasonable precautions which are appropriate to the nature of the information to prevent and minimize such risks in connection with your use of this site.

## Accuracy of Collected Data 

Global Hotelindex will on its own initiative, or at your request, free of charge, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by Global Hotelindex in connection with the operation of this site. Please consult the contact information posted below on this page, if any, or elsewhere on this site to determine how best to contact Global Hotelindex to update and/or review your personal data and/or opt out of receiving marketing communications from Global Hotelindex.

## Minors 

Global Hotelindex's policy is to request that "Minors" (the age of Minors is determined by local law where you reside) do not make purchases or engage in other legal acts on this site without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless permitted by applicable local law. 

## External Links 

This site may contain links to other sites. Please note that Global Hotelindex is not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of any other sites. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of such sites. 

## Changes to this Policy 

Global Hotelindex may from time to time change this Policy or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice. However, if this Policy is changed in a material, adverse way, Global Hotelindex will post a notice advising of such change at the beginning of this Policy and on this site's home page for 30 days. We recommend that you re-visit this Policy from time to time to learn of any such changes to this Policy.

Copyright Â© Global Hotelindex Ltd, 2008. All rights reserved.
